

CONTACT

- **** 01007981850
- ✓ elghani888@gmail.com
- O Damanhur, Al Buhayrah, Egypt

EDUCATION

2020 - 2024 DAMANHUR UNIVERSITY

• Information system degree

SKILLS

- Project Management
- Public Relations
- Teamwork
- Time Management
- Effective Communication
- Critical Thinking
- Dart
- Flutter
- Dealing with firebase
- Dealing with thunder client API

LANGUAGES

- Arabic (Fluent)
- English (Basics)

MOHAMED ABD ELGHANY

MOBILE DEVELOPER

PROFILE

Highly educated, bilingual professional, with more than 1 year spent pioneering new technologies. Successful and punctual with exceptional debugging skills. Seeking an opportunity to lead a team and create dynamic apps for the Android marketplace.

WORK EXPERIENCE

graduation project

Android Developer

2023 - MAY/2024

- The graduation project was about implementing a smart safety system to help supervisors, managers, workers and other stakeholders to enhance their safety and the work performance.
- My task was:
- developing an Android application to handle the data from worker's helmet and the maintenance process for the system.
- Using the stream functions to ensure that data will be changed in realtime, so the system can reduce the response time for accidents.
- Configure the mobile app with firebase.

CURDS application

OCT2023 - DEC 2023

Android Developer

developed (curds) app to handle a mobile store data with the Add,
Delete, Update, Restore functions.

freelancer

2023 - PRESENT

Android Developer

- In this duration, i built a high performance flutter apps for android.
- I used firebase as database to store the values, images and other data.
- Developed mobile applications tailored to client requirements utilising native technologies.
- Optimised interfaces between hardware and software to enhance usability.
- · Designed and developed software systems using initial brief.
- developed many applications like: music app,to_do_list with authentication feature,.